Andrew Hyte



SKILLS PROFILE

Computer Science: Excellent object oriented programming background. Passion for web development. Fluent in **Java C++ JavaScript HTML CSS3.**

Experienced with C# Python Oracle SQL EXT Node Angular Firebase MongoDB AWS WPF.

Currently developing a web app using **Firebase** with **Angular** and the new firebase hosting capabilities.

Personal and Communication: Experience in handling accounts, collections, and physical transactions. Developed personal skills through years of experience in the workplace, along with customer relations experience.

EDUCATION

B.S. Computer Science,

Brigham Young University, Provo, UT

Dec 2015

GPA 3.23

Associates General Arts

Weber State University, Ogden, UT

Jan 2013 GPA 3.6

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Intern

June 2015 - Aug 2015

Lockheed Martin Mission Systems and Training, Orlando, FL

- Worked on aviation simulation software using C# .NET.
- Took on a database synchronization project which saved the systems team hundreds of man hours of manual data comparison.
- Designed and developed new UI features for project infrastructure tools using C# and WPF.

Full Stack Programmer

Apr 2014-Present

Missionary Training Center, Provo, UT

- One of 5 developers working on a 2.2 million dollar project.
- Developed new features of an online chat application found at Mormon.org which is exposed to 650,000 users per month.
- Wrote code for a Java and Oracle SQL backend and an Angular/Sencha.js frontend.
- Worked in an Agile Scrum environment using Jira for 3 week sprint management.
- Used a Git Flow branching model for repository management.

Product Marketing Intern

Sept 2013-Dec 2013

Go GungHo Inc., Provo, UT

- Created a program in Java using the Twitter API which could be used to contact 1000 new prospective customers from the company's target market per day.
- Worked in a group of four college students to put together a full replicable marketing plan to drive product sales with students on college campuses.

SERVICE

International Volunteer Leader

Oct 2008-Oct 2010

Brazil, Londrina LDS Mission

- Trained and mentored a group of about 30 missionaries in a leadership position.
- Learned to communicate fluently in the Portuguese language.